<resources>
    <string name="app_name">falaksign</string>
    <string name="back">back</string>
    <string name="chatbot">tochatbot</string>
    <string name="send">send</string>
    <string name="hint">أكتب رسالة</string>


    <string name="earth">Earth: Our home planet has a dense metal core,\na thick viscous rock mantle, and a thin crust.
                            \nIt\'s unique in the solar system for having humans\nand liquid water on its surface.</string>
    <string name="moon">Moon: At 3470 km in diameter, the Moon has the\nlongest moon-to-planet ratio.
        It\'s thought to\nhave formed when a small planet impacted\nEarth at a
        grazing angle billions of years\nago. It\'s heavily crated, and has huge\nflood plains on it called mania.</string>
    <string name="jupiter">Jupiter: A gas giant, it\'s the largest planet in\nour solar system. It has a dynamic\natmosphere,
                        including belts, zones,\nand a gigantic red spot created by a\npersistent hurricane. Its interior
                        is mostly\nmetallic hydrogen, and it has the fastest spin of all planets.</string>
    <string name="mercury">Mercury: Orbiting the sun in just 89 days, it also has\nthe most elliptical orbit of any planet.
                        \nIt spins very slowly, once every 2/3\nof its orbital period. Despite its\n
                        surface reaching a blistering 430C,\nit still has water ice in permanently\nshadowed crates
                        near its poles\nwhere the temperature stays below -170C</string>
    <string name="sun">Sun: Our star is 2 octillion tons of hot hydrogen gas\nemitting 400 septillion of energy every
                        \nsecond. The hottest part of the sun is its 15\nmillion C core, when it\'s
                        been fusing hydrogen into helium for the past 4.6 billion years.\nDespite that
                        it\'s only midlife aged!</string>
    <string name="mars">Mars: Its iconic red color comes from its rusty\nrocks and dust. In the past Mars was once
                        \nvery wet, with oceans, a thick atmosphere,\nand a warmer climate.\nBut its lack
                        of a magnetic field meant no protection from\nthe solar wind, which eroded its atmosphere away.</string>
    <string name="venus">Venus: The planet with the hottest surface temperature, at 460C it\'s hot enough to melt lead.
                        Its air is almost entirely composed of carbon dioxide, with a thick layer of sulphuric clouds.
                        Its rotational axis is flipped upside-down, which means the planet spins backwards.</string>
    <string name="europa">Europa: Possessing a water ocean under its icy crust, some scientists have theorized it may be
                            capable of supporting life. These lifeforms might be similar to those on Earth that live
                            next to thermal vents.</string>
    <string name="saturn">Saturn: A gas giant with a broad set of rings. It has a hexagonal cloud pattern on its north pole. It is
                        the least dense of all the planets, even less than water!</string>
    <string name="titan">Titan: Larger than Mercury, it\'s the only moon that has a dense atmosphere. It has methane
                        cycle that is similar to Earth\'s water cycle, including rain and other weather events.</string>
    <string name="uranus">Uranus: An ice giant with a small rocky core and a thick mantle of ammonia, water and methane. It
                        has thirteen distinct rings.</string>
    <string name="neptune">Neptune: An ice giant, with a similar composition to Uranus. It\'s the most dense gas giant planet
                        and the only planet found by mathematical prediction rather than by empirical observation.</string>
    <string name="pluto">Pluto: Discovered in 1930 and categorized as a planet until 2006 when it was re-categorized
                        as a minor planet. Similar large icy bodies have been found beyond neptune, including
                        Eris, Makemake, and Haumea.</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

</resources>